Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - Reel-to-reel tapes, 154445
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les pirouettes vocales pour les pirouettements vocaux" (PT 182), 1995 December; 154532; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 3/4 inches; 00:05:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502795)
        Voix de l'aueur. Vitesse 38 cm (or 15 inches), stéréo; 5'30
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&651fb21e-94e6-4b16-bae0-b4fdfa91606f
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dialogue desourds" (PT 186), undated; 154531; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:10:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888900)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3ee81ba3-e943-4ae3-a74a-a22352c0e27f
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cantata for two farts and Juan Carlos the first" (PT 187), undated; 154530; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 3/4 inches; 00:12:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888918)
        Cantata. Cofie. 7 1/2, stereeo; complète avec Jean
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&784a33a3-4967-4b48-bf2f-a37f71ee992e
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le parlement Européon" (PT 188), undated; 154529; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 1/2 inches; 00:07:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888926)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&82261bc1-4ef4-4ff5-adf4-de88e75e63e4
      - Chopin, Henri. "La flûte des respirs" (PT 189), 2003 May; 154528; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:12:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888934)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a714e295-724e-4ee5-8f61-9a63b17c9242
      - Chopin, Henri. "Discours ministre" (PT 196), undated; 154527; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:03:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888942)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&375f11d8-7185-4c3b-ac9f-4c218ad1e977
      - Chopin, Henri. "DELFT" (PT 197), 1970 November 6; 154526; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:02:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888959)
        Recording with nine students in school en direct et simultane; 19 cm, 2'45"
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ef562728-6030-4060-ac73-5635a0eaea54
      - Chopin, Henri. "Discours des ministres" (PT 198), undated; 154525; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:03:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888967)
        Portrait - Petales
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0c7222c0-5603-4cc4-899e-6ec7f752b951
      - Chopin, Henri. "Soleil mètalique plus clair" (PT 200), undated; 154524; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:09:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888975)
        Original - soleil plus clair; 19 cm.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&96196ffa-0f46-4b7c-b170-090c8961c138
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le chanson du parlement Européen" (PT 202), 1968; 154523; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 inches; 00:01:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888983)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9d7fc54b-6056-48f8-8e65-f534a5e2861a
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le roc aux peaux grumelées" (PT 204), 2004 April; 154522; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 inches; 00:03:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109888991)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&18e27568-64cf-4ae4-a3ae-54e78a386c60
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le ventre Bertini" (PT 205), undated; 154521; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 inches; 00:12:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889007)
        Original. Vietre Bertini 67
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bb87d2bb-13dd-4c75-a24f-6474d0d44379
      - Chopin, Henri. "Tape 2 Revox" (PT 212), undated; 154520; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:09:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889015)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4c6225d0-a009-4fe1-8a43-d78950470a6c
      - Chopin, Henri / Cobbing, Bob. "Vive Rabelais" (PT 159), 1968 November 3; 154519; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:12:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Speed fluctuations can be heard throughout the program. (Box 39, Item barcode 39002109889023)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dcf0ab0e-adc8-4a3e-9419-3287e1efbf50
      - Chopin, Henri. "Plus j'avance plus je vis" (PT ?) (empty case), 2003; 154518 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889734)
      - Chopin, Henri. " Les chaos naturels" (PT ?) (empty case), 2003; 154517 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889742)
      - Chopin, Henri. Untitled (PT ?) (empty case), undated; 154516 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889759)
      - De Vree, Paul and others. "Holland" (PT 184), undated; 154515; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:31:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889031)
        1. Hetleren es en baccaret 2. Kinorama 3. Exodus 4. Oranon 5. Reveil du Chaos 6. Hommage à Orff 7. Papyrofonic
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d18d502d-acd2-488e-a144-ff9abc2a398a
      - Giorno, John / Gysin, Brion. "Subway sound / Bird song / American eagle" (PT 192), undated; 154514; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:10:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program sounds distorted at times. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889049)
        Text by John Giorno; Sound + voice by Brion Gysin; 7 1/2
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&14674fb0-eeae-4b27-b45a-f3c8461925f5
      - Goethals, Lucien. "Polifonium" (PT 34), undated; 154513; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:11:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502803)
        Raffost composition avec audio-poem pour Li magnétos.19 cm; mono
        2.2 De Uitvoering
        2.2.1. Monistisch kunstwerk
        2.2.2. Dualistisch kunstwerk
        2.2.3. Gemengd.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9420b887-58ad-491e-aee5-052e53c64c3e
      - Greenham, Lily. "Relativity / Traffic / Tune in to reality" (PT 96), 1973-1975; 154512; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:27:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889056)
        Lily Greenham, Lingual music, stereo 7 1/2 for 1) Relativity and 2) Traffic 3) "tune in to reality", tapespeed 3 3/4 (9,5) stereo (1/2 - track)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d01e850c-3404-46a4-bb00-97c90252540b
      - Greenham, Lily. "Seven consonants in space" (PT 172), 1975; 154511; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:03:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889064)
        1/2-track, stereo
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bfd84b1d-729b-4289-9eba-9a87d66ecbb8
      - Gysin, Brion. "Pistol poem" (PT 37), undated; 154510; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:17:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502811)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a83661a1-3116-4540-9c8c-63cfffc8e2c4
      - Gysin / Heidsieck / Chopin. "Petite anthologie" (PT 122), 1960-1962; 154509; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:20:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program can be heard only in the left channel from about 13:30 until the end of the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502829)
        Domaine poétique, Paris - I radio; 3'25, 19 cm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&996b8030-cc26-4044-ac81-fdb13622469b
      - Hanson, Sten / H. Chopin. "Double extension" (PT 46), undated; 154508; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:12:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is multi-tracked. All four tracks are played back simultaneiously. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502837)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&de59c879-13e6-4c17-9e62-ea4c3ebc9497
      - Hanson, Sten. "Sine tone 5000 HZ for adjusting the level / Sine tone 10000 HZ... / Intermission/ Don't hesitate do it, do it right now / Intermission..." (PT 52), 1969 August; 154507; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:08:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Digital-sounding static can be heard around 07:40 on the tape. (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502845)
        2-track stereo tape, speed 38 cm/s; recorded at EMS, Stockholm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&641be458-6724-44b6-abab-fd4ba96a38f8
      - Hanson, Sten. "Dance figure (for E.P.)" (PT 169), undated; 154506; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:01:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889072)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6bfc4998-95f6-438f-8a90-67a4e96326ce
      - Hanson, Sten. "Revolution / Dance figure / Railroad poem" (PT 180), undated; 154505; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 3/4 inches; 00:07:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 45, Item barcode 39002104502852)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&56804848-1b39-4a27-9aa1-b6a6e4eec361
      - Heidsieck, Bernard and others. "Heidsieck - Dufrêne - ? - Chopin" (PT 140), undated; 154504; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:15:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889080)
        19 cm.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0c527c46-3f94-444c-85b5-288ce522f1ca
      - Heidsieck, Bernard. "B2B3 - Exorcisme" (PT 207), undated; 154503; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 1/4 inch; 00:04:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889098)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d5d4bb04-8af9-402f-86df-3381bca660a4
      - Hodell, Åke. "Numro ba besch" (PT 147), undated; 154502; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:03:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889106)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bd1ce03d-9ff9-4182-bbdc-7e180aff7a29
      - Jandl, Ernst. "Vom Lautgedicht" (PT 199), 1974; 154501; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 1/4 inches; 00:05:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889114)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6367d571-41ba-4966-b584-cee56c01af02
      - Joyce. "Finnegans Wake extrait" (PT 77), undated; 154500; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:22:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889783)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&40bef78b-d85e-4b1e-9e9b-6962741cc04a
      - Kucharz, Lawrence. "City street scenes I" (PT 149), undated; 154499; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:11:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889122)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&040c11d1-b09b-4c19-b384-1c422e6f522b
      - Kucharz, Lawrence. "City street scenes II" (PT 156), undated; 154498; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:11:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889130)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a23c7df1-df3f-4858-9b9f-02597a41c93b
      - Küpper, Leo / Frison, Jean-Claude. "Le rêveur au sourire passager" (PT 193), undated; 154497; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:19:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889148)
        copie I9 c/s piste pleine, (droits: studio de musique électonique, buxelles)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d8592f36-7f4b-4203-b2e5-413abc9a136e
      - Küpper, Leo. "Innominé" (PT 177), undated; 154496; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:09:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507141)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3d373493-6abd-498c-9eee-719c83a0d115
      - Leonard, Tom. " Déclamations dérivés" (PT 79), undated; 154495; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:05:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889791)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&728b7352-726d-43b1-b7ad-8daff2689d62
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. " 6 phonèmes" (PT 112), undated; 154494; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inches; diameter 7 inches; 00:27:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889809)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&67471eba-9acb-402a-8c11-8e5bba558949
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. "Phonèmes 7-8" (PT 208), undated; 154493; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 1/4 inches; 00:10:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889155)
        Vitesse 19., stereo; pour H. Chopin
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e9d9664d-2e7a-4abe-9207-52156ea90e91
      - Lora-Totino, Arrigo. "Intonation 5 o ..." (PT 95), 1974; 154492; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:25:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889163)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2f27f310-b51f-479d-aa47-ccc4121d7879
      - Lovano, Maguy / Munro, Vincent. "5 cris gestes" (PT 165), undated; 154491; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4; diameter 5 inches; 00:09:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889171)
        Paris, France; 19 cm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0f38d53f-dff7-4241-bcd5-273d40cde886
      - Lund. "Poi poi" (PT 121), undated; 154490; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 01:14:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Speed fluctuations can be heard at 48:30 and for the last minute of the tape. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889817)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e7b5311b-9de3-4767-941c-6acc072bd5cd
      - Lund. "I am..." (PT 123), undated; 154489; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:18:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889825)
        There is a list of five tracks described on the cover.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&cde96b60-b6aa-4464-981a-cd73be6b13ce
      - Miccini, Eugenio. "Alfabeto" (PT 155), 1978; 154488; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:45:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889189)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ac48f920-b183-489d-bfd7-605a638c11f5
      - Mon, Franz. "Ja / Nein Parabel" (PT 157), 1971-1978; 154487; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:03:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 40, Item barcode 39002109889197)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d0f687e9-ad20-46f5-9f3d-96a816fe6e74
      - Novak. "Poèmes onomatopées" (PT 113), 1958; 154486; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:17:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889833)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b3564908-2f88-4d66-93a2-9cea131f5402
      - Orton, Richard. "Kiss" (PT 211), 1969; 154485; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:06:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889205)
        A note from Richard Orton of Lyons Concert Hall, University of York, is included with the reel. It reads: Dear Henri - A kiss for you. Richard; stero 2-track, reduction from 4-track, 7 1/2 ips; realised at the York University Studio for Electronic Music
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b9e03ef9-ad03-4278-8442-48ffa7ecd8d9
      - Peto / v.d. Kooy / Doesburg. "Judy" (PT 201), undated; 154484; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:06:48 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889213)
        19 cm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1ebc7881-4f00-425b-95a4-0bcdfc6baf82
      - Rühm, Gerhard. "Auditive Texte" (PT 190), 1971-1975; 154483; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:18:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889221)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9efa8db4-ef38-4bf1-bc79-f2abbcc82eca
      - Rühm, Gerhard. "Spricht über auditive Poesie" (PT 203), 1977; 154482; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 inches; 00:05:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889239)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&184a4db2-fa98-49c8-bc50-db1dcad30fcd
      - Ruppenthal, Stephen. "Two text-sound compositions" (PT 56), 1975-1978; 154481; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:12:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889858)
        A note on the cover, dated 1978-11-16, reads: For Henri, from Stephen with the greatest admiration for your work. Bravo! Other information on formatting includes: stereo, 2-track, 7 1/2 ips (19 cm).
        Compositions
        Kakao-Poetic Lippudenies of the Ungumptious (1975)
        Improvisation for Processed Voice & Electronics (1978)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&68bd580d-2c17-4031-99ea-beb059a88dbf
      - Sarenco. "English course" (PT 143), 1976-1978; 154480; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:18:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is recorded at a very low level. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889247)
        Improvvisazione Vocale Collettiva: Balon Baleur (1978), Calaone-Baone (PD), Italy; 19 cm/sec, 2 piste, stereo
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7272432b-63e6-4e6d-95f0-3fa316630638
      - Unknown. "Schwitters Sonate in Urlauten" (PT 97), undated; 154479; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:05:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Pockets of silence from 03:44-04:17 and 04:30-05:36 recorded on the tape. Static can be heard in the audio. The program is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889254)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&48ee63f8-d41c-4de5-b205-dce3800adea7
      - Settles, Roberta. "Divertissements" (PT 119), 1973; 154478; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:13:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889841)
        Swedish Radio/Fylking En; text - Sound Festival; 7'00" - 38
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&45a69618-c333-4c1e-9d6e-be00baeba6ad
      - Seuphor, Michel. Untitled (PT 162), undated; 154477; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 3/4 inches; 00:19:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889874)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&72fd2967-cc67-4c8e-ac94-6d7a8817d47f
      - Texier, Marc. "Souffles" (PT 179), 154476; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:02:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889866)
        marc texies; 19 cm/s, durée 4'
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b6d2b1ca-8627-486a-91c4-7a91b9cb6e58
      - Toby. "Father of our thoughts" (PT 55), 2007; 154475; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:09:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889890)
        TOBY, Second generation in 1/2 track @ 7 1/2 IPS
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f70a77c9-1e44-4673-9d21-b516a612d4c2
      - Trio d'Eté. Untitled (PT 14), 1979 July 31; 154474; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:24:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507174)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b1f34d4c-30f4-467d-9536-8bbdbd863190
      - Tristan, F. "Mystère IV" (PT 195), undated; 154473; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:03:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is recorded at a high level and is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889262)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f8e47ed6-d12e-48a7-819c-236b0470e9a3
      - Unknown (PT 209), undated; 154472; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 4 inches; 00:06:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889270)
        2° version
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5af80432-7968-4073-b0d7-6ef5ed04b12a
      - Unclear (either Chopin or Da Silva) (PT 134), undated; 154471; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 01:18:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889288)
        piste 1; WB faire le ler avec 4 p.m. pour 73; 2° sans pm pour 72; Le discours des ministres 38/[?]
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4fa8c28c-ff8f-4bc2-a88e-294ea87d26f2
      - Unknown. "Silencio" (PT 171), undated; 154470; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 01:32:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. A warble can be heard on the tape from 25:00 to 31:20 at times. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889296)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&793de1b0-f12c-4306-ac74-6a9116a0f8e2
      - Unknown. "Les quatre dernières et émissions de H.C." (PT 98), undated; 154469; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:40:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the reel. A high amount of hiss can be heard from 20:31 to the end of the reel. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889304)
        Dêbut.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ad669b5d-b850-4725-bff6-393e5d1ca7a6
      - Unknown (PT 191), undated; 154468; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:35:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889320)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1d4d9249-6f57-4b61-b8a8-6356022a1e2f
      - Unknown. "Vocabularia / Pesciaria" (PT 194), 1977; 154467; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:10:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 41, Item barcode 39002109889338)
        Italy
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8aeca1c3-4003-413c-a1d7-7d7e08982266
      - Unknown. "Le palaois enchanté" (PT 31), undated; 154466; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:41:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889882)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&73d04730-3833-42af-860b-4470c25de75f
      - Unknown. "Tellurgie" (PT 35), undated; 154465; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:10:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889908)
        No. 2
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&07118aae-fde7-42f8-86d5-f35e7a356d35
      - Unknown (PT 42), undated; 154464; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:14:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 46, Item barcode 39002109889916)